export const quizQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'What is an espresso?',
        options: [
            'A sweeter type of coffee.',          
            'A type of beverage made with steamed milk.',
            'A ground coffee that\'s brewed under pressure.',
            'A type of coffee that contains high amounts of caffeine.'
        ],
        answer: 'A ground coffee that\'s brewed under pressure.',
        id: 'q1',
    },
    {
        question: 'A cup of black coffee has how many calories?',
        options: [
            '1 calorie.',
            '10 calories.',
            '50 calories.',
            '100 calories.'
        ],
        answer: '1 calorie.',
        id: 'q2',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is a mocha?',
        options: [
            'A drink also called latte.',
            'A drink made with espresso and steamed milk.',
            'A drink made with espresso and whipped cream only.',
            'A drink made with espresso, steamed milk and chocolate.'
        ],
      answer: 'A drink made with espresso, steamed milk and chocolate.',
      id: 'q3',
    },
    {
        question: 'What are Robusta and Arabica?',
        options: [          
            'Types of iced coffee.',
            'Types of coffee beans.',
            'Types of coffee drinks.', 
            'Types of coffee plants.'
        ], 
        answer: 'Types of coffee beans.',
        id: 'q4',
    },
    {
        question: 'What do you call espresso with hot water?',
        options: [            
            'Latte.',
            'Macchiato.',
            'Americano.',
            'Cappuccino.'
        ],
        answer: 'Americano.',
        id: 'q5',
    },
    {
        question: 'How did the term espresso originate?',
        options: [
            'It\'s Greek for “strong beverage.”',
            'It\'s French for “bitterest coffee.”',            
            'From its Latin root meaning “under pressure.”',
            'It was term invented by an Italian coffeehouse.'],
        answer: 'From its Latin root meaning “under pressure.”',
        id: 'q6',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the biggest consumer of coffee globally?',
        options: [            
            'Norway.',
            'Iceland.',
            'Finland.',            
            'Netherlands.',
        ],
        answer: 'Finland.',
        id: 'q7',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which sentence is true?',
        options: [       
            'Decaf means caffeine-free.',                      
            'An americano is a short coffee.',
            'Brazil grows the most coffee in the world.',
            'Black tea has higher amounts of caffeine than coffee.',
        ],
        answer: 'Brazil grows the most coffee in the world.',
        id: 'q8',
    },
    {
        question: 'In which country did the frappé coffee originate?',
        options: [   
            'Spain.',
            'Brazil.',   
            'Greece.', 
            'France.',
        ],
        answer: 'Greece.',
        id: 'q9',
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the only US state that grows coffee?',
        options: [       
            'Hawaii.',                    
            'Vermont.',
            'Maryland.',
            'Mississippi.',

        ],
        answer: 'Hawaii.',
        id: 'q10',
    },
  ];